I wish I may, I wish I might, become my sister for a night!
Wish Upon a Star is a tv movie, family, comedy film directed by Blair Treu.
A younger sister wishes to switch places with her popular older sister and the
two bickering siblings awaken to find the wish has come true.
Alexia Wheaton, played by Katherine Heigl.
Hayley Wheaton, played by Danielle Harris.
Kyle Harding, played by Donnie Jeffcoat.
Ben Wheaton, played by Scott Wilkinson.
Nan Wheaton, played by Mary Parker Williams.
Mittermonster, played by Lois Chiles.
Wish Upon a Star is a 1996 American fantasy comedy-drama television film directed by Blair Treu,
written by Jessica Barondes, and starring Katherine Heigl and Danielle Harris.
The film focuses on two teenage sisters who magically swap
bodies after wishing on a shooting star.
The tagline of the film is "I Wish I May, I Wish I
Might, Become My Sister For A Night!".
The film explores themes of high school, sibling
relationship, comet, body-swap, teen comedy.
The tone is lighthearted.